Next step is to create a AWS budget.
Very, very important. So let's say if you spin up a database
on AWS later in the program
and you forgot to turn off, you might get a huge bill.
And to avoid that, go to YouTube, look at any of the videos,
and create three budgets.
Budget, one for $10 budget, two for 20 budget,
three for $30.
This will help you get email alerts when your expense on AWS
is going to be hitting that amount,
or it's crossing that amount.
So when you get an email, you can then go
and look at if you have any resource
that is actually still there on AWS,
which is actually getting you this high amount of bill.
So make sure you do that. Do not skip this step.